# BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# Nahuel Brandán







ABOUT ME

Backend Software Developer, with extensive experience in Python, with over 3 years of experience in the industry. Lately worked in the aerospace industry.

Pragmatic. Proactive. Detail-oriented. Has a BS in Computer Science. Promoter of constant improvement in technical documentation and application of good development practices.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Company: <u>Satellogic</u> | 06/2022 - 09/2022

Company specialized in earth observation satellites. Design, manufacture, and operate his own fleet of satellites.

I was part of the backend development team, based on Python, of satellite flight applications, dealing with highly complex problems.

Company: Ascentio Technologies | Project: Sabia-Mar | 08/2021 - 05/2022

Sabia-Mar is a satellite mission, with advanced technology for the study of the sea and the ocean.

I worked as a software developer in **Python**, making contributions to different communication and flight planning modules of the satellite. Developer of both the software and the validation tests. Working with technologies like: Robot Framework, Docker, FastAPI, Django, APIs.

**Company: Incluit** | **Project: Junar** | 03/2019 - 07/2021

- Performing development activities in Python + Django + Django Rest Framework.
- Integration of Autho and Keyclok as a security layer to an API Management.
- Development related to Elastic Search, Redis, Celery.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - (COMPLETED)**

Faculty of Mathematics, Astronomy, Physics and Computing - UNC | 10/2018

Career with strong emphasis on programming, analysis and design of systems, databases and computer networks, without neglecting the theoretical aspects that sustain them.

SELF-STUDY ONLINE COURSES | Platzi | 01/2021 - Present

More than **100 courses completed** and in constant learning in the Platzi professional online academy, on various topics such as: soft skills, English, software development.

# SKILLS (

- Programming languages: Python, C.
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, Elastic Search.
- Frameworks: **Django, FastAPI, Robot Framework.**
- Others: Linux, API Rest, Git, Bash, Autho, Docker, Celery.

### EXTRAS C

English: B1 intermediate.

• Spanish: Native.







